Who are you?
I am Yuwen Jingxuan.
Then...
Then who am I?
Yuwen Jingxuan.
Are you crazy?
Without the Soul Jade, you will become a delirious
and chaotic madman.
How could you make such a big decision
without discussing it with me?
I'm perfectly fine, aren't I?
Then what are you going to do next?
We will cross that bridge
when we come to it.
I'm asking what you plan to do about Miss Tang.
She lost her memory again.
But that's fine.
We can start over again.
Can't we?
Your Highness, have some snacks.
Aren't you afraid I poisoned it?
It's not like you haven't done it before.
No matter what you give me,
I'll eat it anyway.
Your Highness, the palace has sent rewards
to celebrate your birthday.
Please receive the decree.
Today is your birthday.
But why is no one celebrating in the mansion?
I never celebrate my birthday.
I'll be right back.
Today is his birthday.
I should think about what to make for him.
You're back.
Today is your birthday.
I made these longevity noodles for you.
Yunling taught me how to make them.
If they don't taste good,
please don't mind.
You really made these for me?
No one has ever made longevity noodles for me before.
Thank you.
Quick, try them.
They're delicious.
Ah, what's wrong?
Yuwen Jingxuan!
As expected, without the Soul Jade,
it just won't work.
What is a Soul Jade?
Jingxuan has a Soul Jade.
He wears it all year round.
It can stabilize his mind
and relieve his headaches.
But now the Soul Jade is lost.
Is it the jade he mentioned to me before,
the one that looks like my birthmark?
Did he do it to save me?
No wonder he is always moody
and unpredictable.
Zhiye.
Jingxuan, you're awake.
Fortunately, the prescription Miss Tang left
has temporarily controlled your condition.
Where is Miss Tang?
Your longevity noodles got cold,
so she went to make you a new bowl.
You've finally seen the light at the end of the tunnel.
Your Highness, Young Master Su!
Something terrible has happened!
Miss Tang trespassed into the Shang Manor
and has been captured.
Prince Yu sent a message saying that only if you go personally...
Only then can we release them.
Jingxuan.
Sixth Brother, you besieged the royal uncle's private residence today.
Are you going to force the Emperor to abdicate tomorrow?
Prince Shuo, if you stop now,
I can still keep my mouth shut in front of His Majesty.
Otherwise...
Lady Shang is merely a step-empress.
His Majesty has never issued a clear edict.
Lord Shang's title of royal uncle is self-proclaimed.
Since Lord Shang wants to report to the throne,
why don't we go together?
You can impeach me for attacking your private residence,
and I will impeach you for great disrespect.
Young Master Su is unmatched in eloquence.
Uncle, you'd better not argue with him.
Enough nonsense.
Lord Shuo is here.
Hand over Miss Tang.
Oh, Young Master Su, what are you talking about?
Miss Tang is a grown woman.
She can go wherever she wants.
How could I control her?
Besides,
I promised Miss Tang I would grant her every request.
A gentleman's word
is worth its weight in gold.
Miss Tang has sought refuge with me now.
She can stay as long as she likes.
No one can take her away from me.
Yuwen Jingxuan is in danger.
Only you can save him.
Why should I believe you?
Who knows if you are deceiving me?
So everything he said was true.
Tang Zhiluo, only if you keep dying for him,
will the imperial destiny return to its place,
and Yuwen Jingxuan become a wise ruler.
This is what you must accomplish.
Zhiluo!
Go quickly!
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have doubted you.
Don't be sad,
and don't feel guilty.
I'm not just doing this for you,
but also for the people of the world.
I don't want you to go!
Zhiluo!